<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Arka Plan&amp;Obje Kaldırıcı</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_menu">Gizlilik Politikası</string>
    <string name="licences_menu">Lisanslar</string>
    <string name="share_menu">Uygulamayı Paylaş</string>
    <string name="feedback_menu">Geri Bildirim Gönder</string>
    <string name="feedback_dialog_error_text">Email uygulaması bulunamadı.</string>
    <string name="feedback_dialog_send_feedback_button_text">Gönder</string>
    <string name="crop_activity_title">Kırp</string>
    <string name="analyze_image_button_text">Analiz Et</string>
    <string name="error_dialog_text">Fotoğraf analizi esnasında bir sorun oluştu.</string>
    <string name="error_dialog_confirm_button_text">Tamam</string>
    <string name="error_dialog_title">Hata</string>
    <string name="no_result_dialog_title">Sonuç Alamadım</string>
    <string name="no_result_dialog_text">Yüklediğiniz fotoğrafa herhangi bir işlem yapamadım, özür dilerim. Başka bir fotoğraf deneyebilir misiniz?</string>
    <string name="no_result_dialog_confirm_button_text">Tamam</string>
    <string name="storage_permission_rationale_dialog_confirm_button_text">Tamam</string>
    <string name="storage_permission_rationale_dialog_title">İzin Gerekli</string>
    <string name="storage_permission_rationale_dialog_text">İşlenen fotoğrafları kaydedebilmem için depolama izni gerekli.</string>
    <string name="save_button_text">Kaydet</string>
    <string name="save_success_text">Başarıyla Kaydettik!</string>
    <string name="save_error_text">Kayıt esnasında bir hata oluştu!</string>
    <string name="cancel_button_text">İptal</string>
    <string name="open_folder_button_text">Kayıtlı Resimleri Göster</string>
    <string name="open_folder_error_text">Klasör açılırken hata oluştu!</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_dialog_confirm_button_text">Tamam</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_dialog_title">Gizlilik Şartnamesi</string>
    <string name="licences_dialog_title">Lisanslar</string>
    <string name="licences_dialog_confirm_button_text">Tamam</string>
    <string name="subs_dialog_no_product_text">Henüz bir ürün eklenmemiş</string>
    <string name="subs_dialog_products_query_error">Ürünleri sorgularken bir hata oluştu</string>
    <string name="subs_dialog_title">PRO ol, Reklamlar Kalksın!</string>
    <string name="subs_period_weekly_text">Haftalık</string>
    <string name="subs_features_text1">Reklam yok, başağrısı yok</string>
    <string name="subs_features_text2">İstediğin zaman iptal edebilirsin</string>
    <string name="subs_dialog_confirm_button_text">Detayları Gör</string>
    <string name="subs_dialog_cancel_button_text">İptal</string>
    <string name="feedback_dialog_title">Geri Bildirim Gönder</string>
    <string name="feedback_dialog_textfield_hint">Bildiriminiz..</string>
    <string name="failed_load_ad_text">Reklam yüklenemedi, tekrar denenecek.</string>
    <string name="unable_load_ad_text">Reklam yüklenemiyor.</string>
    <string name="get_pro_button_text">PRO\'ya Geç</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">**Privacy Policy**\n\n

This privacy policy applies to the Background Eraser app (hereby referred to as "Application") for mobile devices that was created by Samed Harman (hereby referred to as "Service Provider") as an Ad Supported service. This service is intended for use "AS IS".\n\n\n\n

**What information does the Application obtain and how is it used?**\n\n

The Application does not obtain any information when you download and use it. Registration is not required to use the Application.\n\n\n\n

**Does the Application collect precise real time location information of the device?**\n\n

This Application does not collect precise information about the location of your mobile device.\n\n\n\n

**Do third parties see and/or have access to information obtained by the Application?**\n\n

Since the Application does not collect any information, no data is shared with third parties.\n\n\n\n

**What are my opt-out rights?**\n\n

You can stop all collection of information by the Application easily by uninstalling it. You may use the standard uninstall processes as may be available as part of your mobile device or via the mobile application marketplace or network.\n\n

**Children**\n\n

The Application is not used to knowingly solicit data from or market to children under the age of 13.\n\n\n\n

The Service Provider does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children. The Service Provider encourages all children to never submit any personally identifiable information through the Application and/or Services. The Service Provider encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children\'s Internet usage and to help enforce this Policy by instructing their children never to provide personally identifiable information through the Application and/or Services without their permission. If you have reason to believe that a child has provided personally identifiable information to the Service Provider through the Application and/or Services, please contact the Service Provider (xxsamedx@gmail.com) so that they will be able to take the necessary actions. You must also be at least 16 years of age to consent to the processing of your personally identifiable information in your country (in some countries we may allow your parent or guardian to do so on your behalf).\n\n\n\n

**Security**\n\n

The Service Provider is concerned about safeguarding the confidentiality of your information. However, since the Application does not collect any information, there is no risk of your data being accessed by unauthorized individuals.\n\n\n\n

**Changes**\n\n

This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time for any reason. The Service Provider will notify you of any changes to their Privacy Policy by updating this page with the new Privacy Policy. You are advised to consult this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes, as continued use is deemed approval of all changes.\n\n\n\n

This privacy policy is effective as of 2024-12-12\n\n\n\n

**Your Consent**\n\n

By using the Application, you are consenting to the processing of your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy now and as amended by the Service Provider.\n\n\n\n

**Contact Us**\n\n

If you have any questions regarding privacy while using the Application, or have questions about the practices, please contact the Service Provider via email at xxsamedx@gmail.com.\n\n\n\n

This privacy policy page was generated by [App Privacy Policy Generator](https://app-privacy-policy-generator.nisrulz.com/)</string>
</resources>